

# VALENTIN TUDOSE

FULL STACK SOFTWARE DEVELOPER 

◆ BUCHAREST, ROMANIA 

+40774467219

#### • DETAILS •

Bucharest Romania +40774467219

# tudose.valentin21@gmail.com

• SKILLS •

CSS3

Linux

**Bootstrap** 

Docker

MySQL

PHP

jQuery

HTML

CSS

Java

Git

JavaScript

VueJS

RabbitMQ

SASS

#### PROFILE

Enthusiastic technical professional with a complete understanding of the entire software development life-cycle. Known for having talents in PHP and SQL and also a big fan of microservices architecture and object-oriented programming paradigm.

Having good skills in communication and presentations. Experienced in the full project life cycle from design to implementation to integration.

Also experienced with the agile development methodology.

# EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

## Full Stack Software Developer at Softia, Bucharest

March 2020 — Present

- Rewrite JQuery pages to VueJS.
- Added Vuex state management system for the frontend app.
- Created PostgreSQL functions that retrieved big chunks of data.
- Improve docker images
- Fixed system tests.
- Created Vue components from scratch.

# Technologies used:

• PHP 7.3, Laravel, VueJS 2.4, JQuery, PostgreSQL, Docker.

# Full Stack Software Developer at Frisbo, Brasov

February 2019 — October 2019

Integrated several different warehouse management systems

#### API.

 Performed troubleshooting of technical issues within the production environment.

Wrote server-side and client-side code using PHP,

 ${\it HTML, CSS, and JavaScript, specifically with Angular\,7}$ 

framework on the frontend and lumen on the backend.

• Mentored junior developers to coach on industry

best practices and techniques, resulting in

competent developers and greater product quality.

 The application was written having a "microservices architecture" in mind so I've learned docker as a result Technologies used:

• PHP 7.3, Lumen, Angular, MySQL, Docker, RabbitMQ.

# PHP Software Developer at EMAG, Bucharest

April 2018 — January 2019

 Worked on an internal app called DMS which is short for Delivery Management System.

- Written unit tests
- · Integrated and maintained several different couriers

API such as Fan Courier, Sameday, etc

- · Worked with RabbitMQ message broker
- Create and optimize MySQL gueries for a better app performance
- Helped develop an android application written in Java.

Technologies used:

• PHP, Symfony, JQuery, PostgreSQL, Java, RabbitMQ.

# Full Stack Software Developer at Ubisoft, Bucharest

July 2017 — April 2018

Analyzed requirements and designed, developed

and implemented software applications for multiple

teams in the QC (Quality Control) department.

· Maintained and develop frontend applications with

#### VueJS

Technologies used:

• PHP, Laravel, MySQL, CSS.

# PHP Developer at Stargift, Bucharest

February 2017 — July 2017

• Develop new functionality for the e-commerce

website called www.stargift.ro

• Helped with developing and maintaining a product image preview system.

The product preview system's responsibilities were to take the user photos and generate a new photo where the user photos were displayed as it was printed on the products.

Technologies used:

• PHP, MySQL, CSS, JavaScript and HTML 5

## PHP Developer at BluePink Software, Constanta

July 2016 — December 2020

• Worked on multiple web applications written in a

custom PHP Framework

• I've written MySQL queries for insert, update, delete

resources from database

· Created pagination functionality.

Technologies used:

• PHP, MySQL, CSS, JavaScript and HTML 5

# EDUCATION

Bachelor degree in computer science, Ovidius university, Constanta

October 2013 — October 2016